bark.com 2019-06-24

# Bark Privacy Policy

* * *

Bark.com is a service provided by Bark.com Global Limited of 40 Eastbourne Terrace, London, England, W2 6LG, United Kingdom. This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. Users can access the Bark.com service (the "Service") through our website www.bark.com, through APIs, and through third-parties. A "Device" is any computer used to access the Bark.com Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access to the Bark.com Service, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as "information".

## 1\. The Information We Collect And Store

We may collect and store the following information when running the Bark.com Service:

Information You Provide: When you register an account, we collect some personal information, such as your name, email address, phone number, home and business postal addresses. If you are posting a new buyer request then we will also collect information that request, and you can upload attachments such as images, video or documents to the service. You may also provide us with your contacts' email addresses when sharing requests with them. If you are paying for part of the Bark.com service, then we will collect your billing details, including card details and billing address.

Log Data: When you use the Service, we automatically record information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include the Device’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, and other interactions with the Service.

Cookies: We also use "cookies" to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your Device. We may use "persistent cookies" to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service.

## 2\. How We Use Personal Information

Personal Information: In the course of using the Service, we may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide updates and product announcements.

Geo-Location Information: When using the service we may use your Device’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address to identify your approximate geographical location. Some photos you upload to Bark.com may also contain recorded location information. We may use this information to optimize your experience.

Analytics: We also collect some information (ourselves or using third party services) using logging and cookies, which can sometimes be correlated with Personal Information. We use this information for the above purposes and to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase our Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Service to process their requests. This information includes the date and time of your visit, the source of your visit and demographic information such as your age and gender. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Google Analytics. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, click here, and to learn how to opt out of that service click here.

## 3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your Use: We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). Through certain features of the Service, you may also have the ability to make some of your information public. Public information may be broadly and quickly disseminated.

Service Providers, Business Partners and Others: We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

Third-Party Applications: We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Services through such an application. We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Bark.com Global Limited's Rights: We may disclose to parties outside Bark.com content and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Bark.com or its users; or (d) to protect Bark.com Global Limited’s property rights.

Business Transfers: If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or Files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

Non-private or Non-Personal Information: We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

## 4\. Changing or Deleting Your Information

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your "account settings". If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account settings. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law.

## 5\. Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion.

## 6\. Security

The security of your information is important to us. Whenever you submit content using our service, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
